As Prophet T.B. Joshua ministers prayer and deliverance to the people in Jesus' name,
he encounters this woman and the evil within her is exposed.
She will never be a psychiatrist.
If this girl can be a psychiatrist, the kingdom of darkness will lose.
She prays for patients.
Who gave her this sickness in her hand?
I gave her poison.
Everybody at work hates her.
She will never...
Listen you demon; how did you enter her?
I gave her poisoned coffee.
Deliverance In Jesus' Name
Set Free In Jesus' Name
TESTIMONY CONTINUES
Good Morning, Church!
Amen!
My name is Sewela Setjie.
I am a medical doctor, specializing in psychiatry.
I'm 33 years old and I come from South Africa.
When I came to The SCOAN Easter Service 2017, I had three problems.
I had a problem with my right arm, my wrist.
I also had evil attacks as you saw in the clip, and I was also suffering from depression.
So I came and I was instantly healed from the problem that I had with my arm.
Every time I went to the doctors, they couldn't tell me what the problem was
but I was struggling at work - struggling to write, to function.
When I went home, I later on vomited the poison that you heart the evil spirit
speaking about in the clip.
These are the photos of the poison that I vomited.
So you can see right there is the poison.
The demon confessed that she had been poisoned through coffee
and this was the poison she actually vomited after that day.
You can see it there on her phone.
As you introduced yourself, you said you're a medical doctor
and you specialize in psychiatry.
Yet one of the problems you too were having when you came was depression.
Can you tell us about what God has done concerning that problem you once had.
I got divorced at the age of 26 and I also had a miscarriage.
Since then, I had been harboring deep pain in my heart.
Offence - I was offended at my ex-husband
I was also offended at God because I felt as if God was not with me
when I went through the challenges.
I went into depression; I was struggling at work.
The depression got so severe that at times when was seeing patients,
if I asked a patient what their name was, how old they were,
I would forget the next question I was supposed to ask.
Sometimes, if I was driving, I would forget the direction.
I would have to stop on the way, on the side of the road.
It happened and I almost had an accident.
I had to call the psychiatrist who was treating me, crying for help.
At times if I went to the mall, parked my car, I would forget where the car was when I got out.
I needed to go out, take my remote, switch the car on wherever it was, for me to locate it.
I also later on had suicidal thoughts.
Honestly, being a medical doctor in psychiatry,
seeing what patients are going through
and going through the same thing made it hell.
I couldn't pray, focus or enjoy life.
I had no peace of heart.
I couldn't sleep; I lost so much weight.
Then I just decided that it was better for me to die.
When I was driving to the clinic because I work in Cape Town,
as I drove through passing the ocean, thoughts would come to me,
"Just drive your car into the ocean" - almost every Thursday when I went to the clinic.
So we can see that the depression had really gone to an extreme level.
But you came to The SCOAN and received deliverance.
What happened thereafter?
When I came to The SCOAN, Prophet T.B. Joshua was teaching about forgiveness and unforgiveness.
And he said that a lot of Christians have never experienced the presence of God
because of harboring unforgiveness in their hearts, years of holding offence.
Later on when I went home, I watched the message again.
I meditated on the Word.
To be honest with you, children of God, when the prophet was preaching,
I didn't really think that message was for me;
I didn't really think that that was the cause of the depression.
I had suffered from depression since 2012,
taking medication but nothing was helping.
The more I meditated on the Word of God, that burden in my spirit was released.
And the healing that I was looking for for those many years came instantly.
Hallelujah. Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
Dr Sewela Setjie
Deliverance / Healing Testimony
What has been happening is that now when I was at work,
I started doing my own research in a way on the side.
Most of the patients that came into my room were suffering from depression.
I would later ask them, "Madam, is there anybody that has hurt you in your life?"
I'm talking about people at the age of 60,
I'm talking about pastors' wives,
I'm talking about old men,
coming and crying and confessing that "Yes, in fact I was hurt".
I used the same sermon that I received,
the same word that I received from Prophet T.B. Joshua to minister into their lives.
Glory be to God.
And we know at that time, you had explained that apart from treating patients,
you had also began to treat yourself, taking medication.
What did you do with the medication?
The prophet said, "If you don't believe in God with your medication,
you will not believe in Him without your medication".
How or when I stopped taking the antidepressants - I will not tell you.
It came automatically.
I just started sleeping without it and I was able to sleep.
In fact, I was sleeping so much that I said,
"God, this is too much.
I think You have healed me way too much".
I started enjoying life.
It is very painful for people to look at you and think, "Oh, you are successful";
to look at you from the outside and see you are dressed well,
but they don't know that what is going on in your heart
is even worse than cancer that people can see.
I give You glory Lord
As I honour You
You are wonderful
You are worthy oh Lord
Amen! She has said it all. Congratulations!
And as your word of advice, let us know that we should refuse to be offended.
We have no right to hold offence whether offended or offender
as we all stand in helpless need of divine forgiveness.
Thank you so much for sharing your testimony.
You are blessed; continue to share it with others, in Jesus' name.
TT: Lizz Ndungu 25/09/2018
RV: Mel Flowers 04/11/2018